export const QuizData = [
    {
        id: 0,
        question: "hello hello :> thank you for putting up with me when I do stupid shit in Cabot and when I exquisitely roast you! you are so big brain but more importantly you are an incredibly sweet and caring person. and also you are big brain. and also your kat score is equal to 1. did I mention that you are big brain? happy birthday to our favorite sna- i mean CS guru! <3 -- stanvardexpedia",
        options: ['Kathryn Zhou', "Raymond Feng", 'David Ma', 'Hahn Lheem'],
        answer: "Raymond Feng"
    },
    {
        id: 1,
        question: " HAPPEE BIRTHDAY KATTIAN!!!!! I'm so happy to have gotten to know this amaaaazing person better and better from mc17 to sparc18 and college19-23 :)))) my kat score is probably <3 (hahaha get it <3 is an expression but also an emoji okay I will stop now) can't wait for more fun times to come :D -- -1 brain cell",
        options: ['Jenny Hong', 'Karly Hou', 'Moses Mayer', "Max Guo"],
        answer: "Max Guo"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: " Kat -- so great getting to know you this semester! Honored to welcome you to the 55 pset gang. Keep living the snake life sssssssssss",
        options: ["Sheldon Tan","Ivan Specht"," Matthew Hajjar"," Claire Zhou"],
        answer: 'Ivan Specht'
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: " Happy birthday Katty T.  -- Señor Halback ",
        options: ["Your Old Spanish Teacher","Salvador Dali"," DJ Lil David Liu","Damon Halback"],
        answer: 'Damon Halback'
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: " HAPPY BIRTHDAY KAT!!! I hope you had an amazing time at Harvard over this past year, and I can’t wait to see you once we get out of quarantine!! It’s always been so fun getting to hang out from lower school to high school of Harker, and I loved our time together in advisory! Wishing you all the best for your birthday and many more to come!!",
        options: [" Anna Wang"," Kat's Harker Jun","Matthew Hajjar"," Kat Zhang"],
        answer: 'Matthew Hajjar'
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "HAPPY BIRTHDAY KAT!! I'm so, so glad we've become closer over the past few years. Sitting next to each other in Computer Architecture was truly a bonding experience 😌Seriously, though, I'm so glad we're friends, because you're such a genuinely fantastic and caring person...and also I'm so happy we have so many mutual friends in college toooo :) Hope you have the best day! -- humanities junkie^TM",
        options: ["Evan Chen","Cindy Wang","Nikhil Dharmaraj","Kat Zhang"],
        answer: 'Nikhil Dharmaraj'
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "HI KAT - i have always admired you so much for your dedication, brilliance, humility, kindness, and ability to laugh no matter what the situation is. although i don’t see you too much around campus, i’m honestly so honored to know someone like you, and your energy continues to inspire me even from afar. from random greetings in cabot to rant sessions about near mitra (oops), i have nothing but fond memories with you. i hope you have the best day ever :) sending lots of love!! i’m aware that you’re guessing the authors of these messages, so i’ll make this simple hehe love, your birthday twin ;)",
        options: ["Melissa Kwan"," David Ma","Asher Noel (lol)","Kelsey Wu"],
        answer: 'Kelsey Wu'
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "Kat Tian! Happy birthday, my love. <3 My first memory of you was your TIAN dollars during StuCo elections back in freshman year. I then learned you were a math god and was like 'holy shit, this girl is way too cool for me.' I still think that you're way too cool for me, but I'm thankful to call you my friend now. There are so many things I admire and respect about you. You literally manage to do everything in the world, succeed in all of them, and still be the cool, chill person that we all know and love. National Econ Challenge, escape room, AP Art History, karaoke, even just random talks on the couches in Shah, etc. — there are so many memories with you that I appreciate (and many more Titanic pictures to prove it). You're the kind of person that people want to have in their lives (which is pretty evident considering how huge this birthday chat for you is HAHA), and I can confidently say that you've managed to impact so many people in such a positive way. I always manage to learn something through my conversations with you. It sucks that we're so far away from each other in college and that I'm absolutely the worst at responding to texts since I miss having you in my life, but I'm happy to see you doing so well. I'm excited for all the things you're doing and what your future holds; let's talk about it sometime over boba or Philz. :) Until then, I hope you have an amazing birthday and the best year! You deserve it. <3  -- the Jack to your Rose <333",
        options: ["Melissa Kwan","Shania Wang","Sidra Xu","Ashley Lin"],
        answer: 'Shania Wang'
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: " hello kat! it's been a great ride from our mathcounts days to research class with spenner. sadly you chose the wrong school, but seems like you're having an ok time there :) catch up soon!",
        options: ["Broken Capitalization Key"," Sian Smith"," Matthew Guo","Raj Movva"],
        answer: 'Raj Movva'
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: " good morning queen. congratulations on turning 19? there's no new legal things for you, but you're one year closer to not being able to share your parents insurance anymore. good news is you also can't get in for free at the philadelphia museum of art. that's also bad news i lied. in conclusion happy birthday!!!!!",
        options: ["Also Broken Shift Key"," Cindy Wang"," Anna Wang","Sian Smith"],
        answer: 'Sian Smith'
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "Hi Kat! You're definitely one of the most talented hikers and rowers I know, I'm glad to have had the chance to learn how to survive in the wilderness with an expert. Ok, but real talk, thanks for being one of the first friends I made at harvard; you're a super kind and genuine person, and I hope you have a great birthday!--the second smartest person you know",
        options: ["Kevin Mao","Jeffrey Kwan","Melinda Sun","Ginnie Ma"],
        answer: 'Kevin Mao'
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: "Happy  Birthday Kat!!  You are a bundle of silly+positive+high IQ energy, and an amazing friend. I'm so glad I met yo that one summer several years ago (and through several more coincidental summers 😉)! tHoUgH you should've come to a certain other school, it's been great meeting up this year on both sides of the coast, and I hope to see you again soon! Have a fantastic bday!! ❤️❤️",
        options: ["Jocelin Su","Emiko Armstrong","Justin Xie","Jacqueline Wei"],
        answer: 'Jocelin Su'
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: "Happy Birthday Kat!! It's been great getting to know you and hanging out together over the past year, especially this sem. Look forward to more Zoom calls and tea sessions over the next few months and see you back on campus soon! (And congrats on being the first and only person to drag me to Cabot ;) )",
        options: ["Damn That Wink Tho","Jeffrey Gu","Kelly Shen","Sheldon Tan"],
        answer: 'Sheldon Tan'
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: "ITS MY FAV RESEARCH QUEENS BIRTHDAY!! happy birthday u godly god i miss art history and advanced research and planning our legendary spenner birthday surprise with you so much!! i know ur killing it at harv and can't wait for more sf train rides and memez when quarantine is over <3 ",
        options: ["Melinda Sun","Christie Chen","Kelly Shen","Ruhi Sayana"],
        answer: 'Ruhi Sayana'
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: "Ahhh Kat my tiny bb I'm so glad that you're close by in college and we get to occasionally hang out :') I'm so proud to watch you thrive and live your best life there!! like look at all the people who came together to do this!! I hope you have the best birthday at home and let's have a math club reunion when this blows over. big love <3",
        options: ["Emiko Armstrong","Joanna Lin","Joanna Ling","Joanna Liu"],
        answer: 'Joanna Lin'
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        question: "Hey Kat! From when we first met, you've always been so incredibly kind and insightful to talk to! You're so amazing in so many regards yet at your core you're a humble, understanding, and admirable person who always helps others! I admire your work ethic and sincerely hope that you take a little bit of a break today and help work on yourself :) You're the epitome of a Harvard/Harker intellectual yet you're so kind hearted at the same time. It was absolutely a blast walking around so far and talking to so many different businesses on that Day of Service and it was honestly super awesome to connect with you!! Take care and please let me know if there's anything I can do for you!!! Have a Happy Birthday :)))) -- day of service buddy",
        options: ["Rachel Li","Derek Zheng","Karen Ge","J.gu"],
        answer: 'Derek Zheng'
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        question: "happy birthday Kat!! can't believe we've known each other for over 13 years now #kthrulife so glad to have gotten closer to you through apah, skiing, and mhyo LOL. you are such an amazing person and constantly an inspiration to those around you! i love youuu and hope you have the best day.",
        options: ["Kat Zhang","Cindy Wang","Justin Xie","Anna Wang"],
        answer: 'Anna Wang'
    },
    {
        id: 17,
        question: "Hi Kat! You've been an amazing inspiration to me ever since we met during MCSP 2017 :DDD I really admire your work ethic, your generosity, and your incredibly brilliant mind. It's been amazing getting to watch you grow and listen to your infectious laugh, to debate life philosophy with you and to learn about algebraic topology XD. Here's to another awesome year of Kat Tian life, which has never failed to make mine so much brighter <3",
        options: ["Haneul Shin","Ashley Lin","Karen Ge","Hahn Lheem"],
        answer: 'Karen Ge'
    },
    {
        id: 18,
        question: "HAPPY BIRTHDAY KAT!! Wish you all the best always! (P.S. can't wait till you sellout/go into academia - glglgl)",
        options: ["Big Sellout Energy","Big Academia Energy","Big Moncler Jackets","Moses Mayer"],
        answer: 'Moses Mayer'
    },
    {
        id: 19,
        question: "KAT TIAN <33 happy birthday!! I've really enjoyed all our experiences together from card games to deep talks, and it's a little sad that though we always live really close to each other we tend to meet up at faraway events. but it's okay bc even if we're seeing each other for the first time in months I still feel like I can talk to you about anything and we can still have super fun spontaneous conversations over text !! (though I still think you could work on your response times :')) you're a precious human being ily and I miss you lots!! let's try to see each other in person more often once we're able to <3",
        options: ["Jun Kim","Ashley Lin","Ellen Dong","Jimmy Lin"],
        answer: 'Ashley Lin'
    },
    {
        id: 20,
        question: "tiAn happy birth!! it's incredible that after 7 years of knowing you we're still close in proximity (except you never visit angery reaccs) and i'm so so grateful to have you as a friend. you've always been someone I can talk to about anything and i hope that never changes <3 i miss our dance show and orchestra shenanigans you've made my life so much more interesting! there's a ton more i can say but i'm working on being less roasty LOL let's get boba after this whole ordeal love you lots~",
        options: ["Arul Kapoor","Cindy Wang","Haneul Shin","David Ma"],
        answer: 'Cindy Wang'
    },
    {
        id: 21,
        question: "It hasn't even been a year after SPARC and I already can't remember anything except for the conversations I had and the people I met – none more genuinely outstanding than you (sorry Max, you're in tier 2).  Thanks for always being there for me, especially given how busy I know you are -- more to come via pm :)  Enjoy the day!",
        options: ["David Liu","David Liu","David Liu","David Liu"],
        answer: 'David Liu'
    },
    {
        id: 22,
        question: "Hey Kat! HAPPY BIRTHDAY, YOU BEAUTIFUL SOUL. I'm so grateful to be friends with someone as wonderful as you – I don't know what I did to deserve it :'). I still remember that random ski trip we were on FOREVER ago (like 6th grade?) and being absolutely amazing by your skiing skill (maybe not the thing you're most known for, but wow I literally will never forget how god-tier you and your dad were HAHA)!!  You're so incredibly talented, kind, and so utterly genuine in everything you do. You're so loved :) I love you lots, and I hope you know that I'll always be here for you.  Have an AMAZING birthday, Kat! from ME good luck guessing who ",
        options: ["Kat Zhang","Christie Chen","Rachel Li","Benji Kan"],
        answer: 'Christie Chen'
    },
    {
        id: 23,
        question: " Hi KAT happy birthday!!! This message comes from a person who has attended the same class with you twice, and will attend the same class for a third time, most likely without you. No more hints...",
        options: ["Dylan Zhou","David Ma","Ellen Dong", "Jeffrey Kwan"],
        answer: 'Jeffrey Kwan'
    },
    {
        id: 24,
        question: "Happy birthday love <3 I'm so proud of you and of how hard you work. I can't wait until the spring when we can finally hang out again in Boston ;) ",
        options: ["Melinda Sun","Kely Shen","Harker Harvard '24 Admit #10","Emiko Armstrong"],
        answer: 'Emiko Armstrong'
    },
    {
        id: 25,
        question: "I hope it's going well! (Your pset, not your birthday.)",
        options: ["Dylan Zhou","David Ma","Justin Xie","Lizzy Ling"],
        answer: 'Dylan Zhou'
    },
    {
        id: 26,
        question: "A sexy beast",
        options: ["Lizzy Ling","Ginnie Ma","Asher Noel","Derek Zheng"],
        answer: 'Asher Noel'
    },
    {
        id: 27,
        question: "HAPPY BIRTHDAY, KAT!!!! I hope you're having a good time at home! Thanks for being such cool, wise, and hilarious friend over the last 3 years! <3  I can't wait for our next food adventure, either next time I'm in the Bay Area (August 4th reunion part 3??) or sometime in Cambridge! Have an amazing birthday!!! <3 <3",
        options: ["Melissa Kwan","Melinda Sun","Jimmy Lin","Kelly Shen"],
        answer: 'Melinda Sun'
    },
    {
        id: 28,
        question: "A sonnet for Kat Tian (pls excuse the veeery sketchy iambic pentameter): //My fairest friend, Kat, we first met that one // Weekend in DC. You are now older. // Since then together we have had much fun. // Some might say that you are getting bolder. // Raymond would say that cats evolve to snakes, // But you’re a beast, big brain, huge PPC,  // I know that you are real and ain’t no fake. // Wish I was on your team, HCCG. // Generic Asian guys and Harker gang, // One-thousand and six friends that is so much, // You have impacted our lives with a bang, // Countless lives that you have helped, loved, and touched. // So thank you Kat, there’s so much more to say, // For now, I will just say happy birthday! -- Shakespeare",
        options: ["Ginnie Ma","Rachel Li","Justin Xie","Kat Zhang"],
        answer: 'Rachel Li'
    },
    {
        id: 29,
        question: "Hi Kat Tian!!!! Happy birthday! It’s crazy that we’ve only known each other for less than a year, but honestly my first year in college would not have been the same without you. From math and stat psets to AADT rehearsals, we’ve made so many amazing memories, and I can’t wait for the next 3 years (and grad school?!)!",
        options: ["Kathryn Zhou","Ellen Dong","Ginnie Ma","Arul Kapoor"],
        answer: 'Ginnie Ma'
    },
    {
        id: 30,
        question: "Hi Kat!! I know we haven't talked a lot this year but you seem like such a chill and cool person--I feel like we relate to each other so much (especially our viewpoints about men lol) and I'm excited to get to know you better next year!! Happy to be linking with you :-) ",
        options: ["Kathryn Zhou","Jacqueline Wei","Lizzy Ling","Karly Hou"],
        answer: 'Jacqueline Wei'
    },
    {
        id: 31,
        question: "Happy birthday Kat! I love and miss you very much and hope that you're doing well at home! I guess the 'see you if things aren't too bad in 2 weeks' isn't happening, but I'm certain we'll get to hang out sometime after quarantine and get Sushi Heaven or Sul & Beans again! Thank you for being so incredibly caring and for inquiring after me and being there for me (although I think we need to work on our keeping in touch skills lol). You are such a quirky person, but I appreciate you all the more for it, and I really miss hearing your roasts all the time. I am extraordinarily glad that we share the same taste for art (JOHANNES VERMEER among others) because otherwise I don't know if we could be friends :P (jk ofc). I have so many wonderful memories with you, from Little Women to Stanford Econ to fooling around in Halback's room during Office Hours, and I can't wait to see you again! Love you and hope you have the best 19th birthday ever! ",
        options: ["Kelly Shen","Benji Kan","Kat Zhang"," Karly Hou"],
        answer: 'Kelly Shen'
    },
    {
        id: 32,
        question: "HI KATTttT HAPPY BIRTHDAY BB you're a mfin s n e k but im still glad ur seniors flaked and i got to meet u in nyc. good to see that quality hs educational experiences like nec are not being wasted on the children and have inspired u to become a sellout. fr tho u the biggest brain and probably make up like 2 of our 7 brain cells and i hope you had the bestest bestest day <3 <3",
        options: ["Haneul Shin","Hahn Lheem","Asher Noel","Jeffrey Gu"],
        answer: 'Jeffrey Gu'
    },
    {
        id: 33,
        question: "Kat/Katty/KattyTDabs/katanada/my shawty bae for life <3 I still remember the day we first met, and it's wild to think that something so funny/silly has turned into a 13+-year friendship, from first grade to senior year and beyond. You've always been one of the most confident, self-assured people that I've known, from playing Gem School and 'Hello, my name is Bye' in 2nd and 3rd grade to making forts in fifth grade to math club in 6th grade to watching you take on the world and blossom as a student and as a person throughout high school and just getting to celebrate all that we've become in senior year.  We haven't had the easiest friendship this whole time, as you might expect from a friendship of 13 years -- for a lot of middle school and early high school, I was dealing with a lot of insecurity and self-doubt, and I couldn't find it within myself to really be happy for other people -- I had to love myself first. But even then, I could tell how much you cared about me and wanted me to be happy -- you were and always have been the first person to cheer me on whenever I accomplished anything, and you'd do the same for anyone in your life. We've been through breakups, ends of friendships, and so many more trials and challenges together, and I couldn't be more thankful to have someone so kind and loyal in my life.  Beyond that, you're one of the most driven and strong people I've met, but you also don't lose sight of your silly side -- you know how to have fun, and I don't think I laugh as hard with anyone else -- nor would I want to. Even so, you know what you're serious about, and you have strong opinions that you're willing to express and defend. You're an incredibly thoughtful person, not only in terms of the things that you do and the people you meet, but also in terms of yourself and what you want out of each and every experience that you've have.  We've come such a long way since we first sat on the benches at recess and read Harry Potter together, or even since we were inseparable in 6th grade math club, and a lot has changed since then, but what I love about our friendship is that we can always pick up where we left off -- seeing you happy and laughing will always make me smile, and seeing you cry will always be more than I can bear.  Happy nineteenth <3 I love you so much and I can't wait for more and more years of getting left on read by you D: -- katexico",
        options: ["The Only Person","Who Would","Write This Much","Queen Kat Zhang"],
        answer: 'Queen Kat Zhang'
    },
    {
        id: 34,
        question: "PUFFLING!! happy birthday! A true honor to be your ~second favorite~ David :) gweagles!!",
        options: ["David Ma","David Liu","David Zhou","David Lin"],
        answer: 'David Ma'
    },
    {
        id: 35,
        question: "Dearest Kat, congratulations on turning 19. It must feel great being as old as a prime number — Z/19Z is a fucking field! isn't that dope. Bro - you're cool, stay dope, and keep learning about art. Art speaks to the soul and opens the windows to the heart; it illuminates the deepest, darkest secrets of one's inner psyche — to see and interpret art is the greatest privilege one can have. Alright, I'm fucking with you. But in all honesty, it's been great going to the same school as you (for many years) and seeing you evolve everyday (like a pokemon!), I hope you've found college fulfilling; feel free to slide into my DMs if you ever want to chat about anything. Have a blast!",
        options: ["Melissa Kwan","Justin Xie","Ellen Dong","Arul Kapoor"],
        answer: 'Justin Xie'
    },
    {
        id: 36,
        question: "Happy Birthday Kat! Can't believe we had such an amazing time at Harker, the HEART and SOUL of the Bay Area, learning about the locations of states and appropriate sleep schedules. Hope you have an awesome day!",
        options: ["Arul Kapoor","Kathryn Zhou","Melissa Kwan","Haneul Shin"],
        answer: 'Arul Kapoor'
    },
    {
        id: 37,
        question: "hi kat!!! happy birthday :))) so glad to have met you this year! ur a pretty amazing gal and always fun to talk to and i am so excited that we're linkmates!!! (oops is this giving too much information) can't wait for more adventures in the future & hope that you get to start some assignments earlier since we're quarantined LOL and that you had a great birthday ❤❤",
        options: ["Karly Hou","Kathryn Zhou","Lizzy Ling","Jacqueline Wei"],
        answer: 'Lizzy Ling'
    },
    {
        id: 38,
        question: "What does a birthday mean? Strictly speaking, it's simply the date that marks one's whole number of trips around the Sun, (almost) uniformly chosen among the 365 each year so that each person has a special day: their own. Socially speaking, society gradually confers legal benefits and removes protections as one progresses through the ranks of age. Practically speaking, it's a fun occasion to celebrate each person, an annual reminder of well-deserved appreciation.  // For you, it means all this (and more!), but... it's also pretty arbitrary, a mere consequence of how civilization has chosen to subdivide time over the years. Not everything has to have intrinsic meaning — you of all people know that best. It can just... be. And that, in and of itself, is meaningful, too. // Enjoy your special day Kat — you deserve only the best :) Happy birthday!",
        options: ["Benji Kan","Melissa Kwan","Ellen Dong","Jun Kim"],
        answer: 'Benji Kan'
    },
    {
        id: 39,
        question: "Happy birthday Kat!! I hope you're having a lovely 19th in the warm weather of Cali!! I'm so sad that we're not on campus together anymore or else I would have gotten you 19 Dove chocolate flavors (though I'm not sure where I'd put them since Kat's Korner is always kind of a mess). Even though you once accidentally made wine from fermented grapes in the minifridge, I couldn't have asked for a better roommate <3 Cheers to the Itty Bitty Titty Committee and have a wonderful day - don't stay up too late !!",
        options: ["Ellen Dong","Melissa Kwan","Jun Kim","Jimmy Lin"],
        answer: 'Ellen Dong'
    },
    {
        id: 40,
        question: "Happy birthday Kat! Thanks for brightening my day every time I see you in Cabot Science Library. When the two of us gang up on David, we are unstoppable. Never forget #youseemprettystressedaboutthis. ",
        options: ["Jimmy Lin","Jun Kim","Melissa Kwan","Kathryn Zhou"],
        answer: 'Melissa Kwan'
    },
    {
        id: 41,
        question: "Happy sbirthday Kat!!! I'm so lucky to have a friend as kind, thoughtful, and compassionate as you. Whether it's about boy problems or about how there aren't enough hard classes for you to take at Harvard or about faith, I'm always so excited whenever we get the chance to catch up and talk about life. You're a truly special person in the way you care about people and kill it at everything you do, and I can't wait for all the memories we'll continue to have together (I really hope you get quadded)! Have an amazing day! ",
        options: ["Jimmy Lin","Patrick Star","Jun Kim","Kathryn Zhou"],
        answer: 'Jimmy Lin'
    },
    {
        id: 42,
        question: "Happy birthday Kat!!! I still remember the first time we met while talking to Jacob at HMMT haha. Who knew we'd be this close just a few years later? :) I'm so happy we got to talk more this semester since we've had more classes in common and through the blocking group hehe. Hope you're doing well at home and I can't wait for the next 3 years :))) <3 ",
        options: ["Haneul Shin","Jun Kim","Melissa Kwan","Kathryn Zhou"],
        answer: 'Haneul Shin'
    },
    {
        id: 43,
        question: "Hi Kat Tian, You are good friends with Kat Zhang. Nice to have met you. K through life all the way! Put them eagles up! Woooo! appy birthday, by the way :) ",
        options: ["Larry Bacow","Jun Kim","Aayush at Princeton","Kat Zhang's Mom"],
        answer: 'Jun Kim'
    },
    {
        id: 44,
        question: "kat tian. i literally love you so much you're my favorite human ever and every time I see you I tell you that LMAOOO. you're the coolest person and so much fun and ofc crazy smart but also a DANCE LEGEND like okay jay park okay renegade!! can't wait for more shenanigans next yr :))) anyways have the best bday my love!!!",
        options: ["Wes","John Harvard","Claire Zhou","Kathryn Zhou"],
        answer: 'Kathryn Zhou'
    }
];